acespirits.com 2013-05-01

# Merwin Liquors - Liquor Store in Minneapolis, Maplewood, and Falcon Heights

_This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the[Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/details.html) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._

 **Our Commitment To Your Privacy** _revised: May 26, 2010_  
Merwin Liquors knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting merwinliquors.com and affiliated websites, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

**What Personal Information Does Merwin Liquors Gather?**  
The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience. Here are the types of information we gather:  
**_Information You Give Us:_** We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you.  
**_Automatic Information:_** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Merwin Liquors. A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit Web sites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist.  
**_E-mail Communications:_** To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Merwin Liquors. if your computer supports such capabilities.  
**_Information from Other Sources:_** For reasons such as improving personalization of our service (for example, providing better product recommendations or special offers that we think will interest you), we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. We also sometimes receive updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily. 

**More About Cookies**  
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits. The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of our features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on. 

**Third-Party Web Beacons**  
We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo!, [click here](https://reports.web.analytics.yahoo.com/optout,OptOut.vm?domain=a.analytics.yahoo.com). 

**Information Sharing**  
Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only with Merwin Liquors, it's subsidiaries and affiliated companies. 

**Business Transfers**  
As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores or assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that Merwin Liquors or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets. 

**Protection of Merwin Liquors and Others**  
We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Merwin Liquors, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

**Information Security**  
We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (credit card number, expiration date, and billing address). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customers' orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. This information is transmitted via our secure server, all your personal information is encrypted before it is transmitted over the Internet, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) to ensure that your information and credit card number are safely transported online. While on a secure page such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. 

**Terms, Conditions and Policies, Notices, and Revisions**  
If you choose to visit merwinliquors.com or affiliated websites, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms, Conditions and Policies, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Minnesota. If you have any concern about privacy, please send us a thorough description to infoo@merwinliquors.com, and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly. This Notice and the Terms, Conditions, and Policies will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. 

**Automatic Information**  
Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; purchase history; the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; products you viewed or searched for; your Auction history, and phone number used to call our 800 number. 

Please don't hesitate to contact us with questions or comments about this web site. 

**Merwin Liquors**  
700 West Broadway  
Minneapolis, MN 55411  
(612)529-9639 (8AM to 10PM CST)  
(612)238-3706 (FAX)  
info@merwinliquors.com
